Guide to the Administrative Services, Yale University, Records of the Director
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Administrative Services, Yale University, records of the director
1951-1987
RU 110
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
38
The records consist of files created and maintained by Radley H. Daly as associate provost for personnel (1975-1979), and director of administrative services (1979-1987). The records document personnel-related functions, including affirmative action, pensions, student employment, labor relations, wages and salaries, benefits, training, and records; parking and communications; printing services; and audio-visual services. Also included are records concerning the university's Committee on Organization and Management of Administrative Services, 1976-1978.
Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
Daly, Radley H.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files created and maintained by Radley H. Daly as associate provost for personnel (1975-1979), and director of administrative services (1979-1987). The records document personnel-related functions, including affirmative action, pensions, student employment, labor relations, wages and salaries, benefits, training, and records; parking and communications; printing services; and audio-visual services. Also included are records concerning the university's Committee on Organization and Management of Administrative Services, 1976-1978.
Personnel management; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Finance; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records, 1968-1977; Accession 1980-A-032
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Administrative Research Office
  - Affirmative Action
  - Publications
  - Staff Analysis
  - Systems and Records
  - University Budget
  - University General
  - Yale Health Plan
  - Miscellaneous
    - Yale Sailing Associates, gifts, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 265)
- Records, 1977-1979; Accession 1983-A-081
  - 1977-1978
    - T-0 Training - General, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - 1978-1979
    - T-0 General, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 217)
- Records, 1979-1980; Accession 1984-A-051
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - T-0 General file, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - T-1 Training Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Records, 1951-1985; Accession 1986-A-051
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
  - Administrative Services, 1980-1981
  - Administrative Services, 1980-1982
    - R - Z, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 105 - 108)
  - Administrative Services, 1981-1982
  - Administrative Services, 1982-1983
    - Yale Literary Magazine Trial (Box 25, Folder 284)
  - Administrative Services, 1983-1984
  - Administrative Services, 1951-1985
    - H, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 391)
    - J, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 393)
    - O, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 400)
    - R, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 402)
    - T, 1979-1983 (Box 34, Folder 405)
- Chronological files and personnel records, 1973-1982; Accession 1986-A-076
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
- Records, 1986-1987; Accession 1989-A-044
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Audio Visual Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Handicapped Committee (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Human Resources (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Operations (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Council of Engineering (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - African Studies (Lacking) (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Records, 1979-1986; Accession 1989-A-050
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - 1984-1985
    - Telephone Contract: Purchase Agreement -- Sonecor, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 1985-1986
    - Y-1 AISEC (International Association of Students in Economics and Commerce), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Y-3 Rideworks, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Records, 1976-1983; Accession 1990-A-052
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - Committee on Organization and Management of Administrative Services
    - University Library Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Agenda, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - General - Operating Policy Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Records, 1971-1986; Accession 1992-A-054
  - University Council Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - January meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)